Steel has existed for thousands of years.
鋼は何千年も前から存在しています。
But it wasn't until the 19th century that it became an essential commodity.
しかし、19世紀まで必須の商品となることはありませんでした。
The invention of the Bessemer process revolutionized the steel industry, spurring the growth of major cities and giving birth to the industrial revolution.
ベッセマー法の発明は鋼鉄業界を革命的に変え、主要都市の成長を促し、産業革命の始まりをもたらしました。
From the construction of towering skyscrapers to the manufacturing of autos and household appliances, steel remains a backbone of civilization.
高層ビルの建設から自動車や家電製品の製造まで、鋼は文明の支柱として残っています。
But the emergence of the modern steel industry has also contributed to the beginning of what would become today's climate concerns.
しかし、現代鋼鉄産業の出現は、今日の気候問題の始まりにも寄与しています。
So the steel industry globally accounts for about 7 to 9% of CO2 emissions. And so there really is this big need to decarbonize.
世界の鋼鉄産業は、二酸化炭素排出の約7～9%を占めています。そのため、脱炭素化の大きな必要性があります。
About 70% of today's steel is produced using the blast furnace method, which relies heavily on coal to generate the heat necessary to reduce iron ore resulting in large amounts of carbon emissions.
今日の鋼の約70%は高炉法を使用して生産されており、鉄鉱石を還元するために石炭を大量に使用しています。その結果、多くの二酸化炭素が排出されています。
Every tonne of crude steel produced using this technique emits around two tonnes of CO2. So Green Steel promises to change this whole dynamic.
この技術を使用して製造された1トンの粗鋼は約2トンのCO2を排出します。そのため、グリーンスチールはこの全体の状況を変えることを約束しています。
Also known as sustainable steel or fossil free steel. Green Steel is a revolutionary concept that aims to transform the industry by replacing coal with clean energy products in the production process.
持続可能な鋼、またはフリー・カーボン・スチールとも呼ばれるグリーンスチールは、製造プロセスで石炭をクリーンエネルギー製品と置き換える革新的なコンセプトです。
Green hydrogen as a substitute to coal in the production process. So to make it simple, well, really replacing coal by wind and solar.
製造プロセスで石炭の代わりにグリーン水素を使用します。つまり、実際には風力と太陽光を利用して石炭を置き換えるのです。
Substituting carbon heavy material with water vapor would bring net steel emissions to essentially zero and create a ripple effect that could reconfigure the structure of the industry and create opportunities for new entrants to be disruptive by making technologies and services more accessible and affordable. But major headwinds remain.
水蒸気を炭素の重い材料で置き換えることにより、純粋な鋼の排出量はほぼゼロになり、産業の構造を再構築し、新規参入者によるテクノロジーやサービスの利用しやすさと手頃さを生み出すことができます。しかし、大きな逆風もあります。
So when we look at the amount of renewable energy that's needed for the steel industry to move towards green steel, we do not have enough clean energy today.
鋼業がグリーンスチールに移行するために必要な再生可能エネルギーの量を見ると、現在では十分なクリーンエネルギーがありません。
The technology required to decarbonize still exists, but significant infrastructure changes are required to support and scale low cost green electricity. Construction of green hydrogen production tools. Iron Reduction facilities and electric arc furnaces are just a few of the necessary investments.
脱炭素化に必要な技術は既に存在しますが、低コストのグリーン電力をサポートし、拡大するためには重要なインフラの変更が必要です。グリーン水素製造装置、鉄還元施設、電気アーク炉の建設などが必要です。
But it isn't going to be cheap. You're going to need a huge amount of capital investment. And in Europe alone, for example, all analysts think that it could cost around $130 billion.
しかし、それは安くはありません。膨大な資本投資が必要となります。例えば、ヨーロッパだけで、およそ1,300億ドルかかるとされています。
Numbers that size, obviously beg the question who will cover the costs? Initiatives are already in place to incentivize the transition and subsidize the upfront investment. One such measure, the United States Inflation Reduction Act, or I.R.A., aims to drive down the cost of key green steel inputs and make the goal of replacing coal with electricity in the production of steel achievable.
そのような規模の数字が、もちろん疑問を呼び起こします。誰が費用を負担するのでしょうか？既に移行を促進し、先行投資を補助するための取り組みが進められています。そのような取り組みの一つ、アメリカのイノベーション削減法(I.R.A.)は、鋼の製造において石炭を電気に置き換える目標を実現するため、グリーンスチールの主要な原料のコストを下げることを目指しています。
The IRA is a game changer in terms of reducing the cost of clean energy in the United States. This provides a truly massive boost in terms of the economics and the scaling of clean energy.
IRAは、アメリカにおけるクリーンエネルギーのコストを削減する面でゲームチェンジャーとなります。これにより経済性とクリーンエネルギーの拡大が実現します。
European policymakers are also sharpening plans to support the transition with funding hydrogen infrastructure investment and carbon border taxes. But further efforts may be needed to make green steel a reality.
欧州の政策立案者も、グリーンスチールを実現するために、水素のインフラ
Achieving net zero carbon neutrality and really halting the impact of climate change is dependent on lots of different factors. But steel is a major contributor of greenhouse gases and steel will continue to be a really important materials globally. So finding a way to decarbonize the sector is really crucial if we are to achieve net zero goals.
ネットゼロの炭素中立を達成し、気候変動の影響を完全に食い止めるためには、様々な要素が必要です。しかし、鋼鉄は温室効果ガスの主要な発生源であり、鋼鉄は今後も世界的に重要な素材となります。したがって、ネットゼロの目標を達成するためには、この分野の脱炭素化方法を見つけることが非常に重要です。
To read our comprehensive blue paper Green Steel 2.0, which details the industry transformation, potential regional deep dives and other key topics. Click the link below.
産業の変革、地域ごとの詳細な分析、そして他の重要なトピックを詳しく解説した当社の包括的なブルーペーパー「グリーンスチール2.0」を読むには、以下のリンクをクリックしてください。